

## **MY CONTACT**

## Phone

+994508269067

## **Email**

simuratli@gmail.com

### **Address**

Baku/Azerbaijan

# **EXPERTISE**

- React is
- Redux
- Sanity io
- HTML/CSS
- Git
- TypeScript
- Zustand

# SIMURATLI ELJAN

# FRONT END DEVELOPER

## ABOUT MYSELF

I am a Front-end developer with 4 years of experience. Interested in the entire Front-end spectrum and working on ambitious projects with positive people. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

## **EXPERIENCE**

UDS Systems, Ukraine, Kiev - (02/08/2021 - present)

Front end (React) developer

As a react developer in UDS Systems company, we develop different solutions for MS Dynamics. Until today I had created 4 tools from start to end and I gave support to the 2 different tools.

Pragmatech, Azerbaijan, Baku - (05/06/2019 - 04/01/2020)

Frontend developer

Here I have mainly developed e-commerce projects and made support for available apps. And also teach students how to become a front-end developer.

Freelance, Azerbaijan, Baku - (20/11/2018 - 12/02/2019)

Frontend developer

When I worked freelance in Baku I made different websites for different costumers

# **EDUCATION**

#### 2016

Computer engineering

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University. Computer engineering

#### 2020

High energy and plasma physics Istanbul University. Department of Physics Faculty of High Energy and Plasma Physics